Guide to the Herndon Dowling Herpetological Collection MS 059
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Species Files (with non-digitized drawings)
  - Calamorhabdium, undated (Box 05, Folder 0177)
    Folder notes: AER XEN; "Batjan" [NR. Halameheap~ (s)] Indonesia, Other markings: RS SE CO 898CAL11
    34023001503780
  - Cercapsis, 1972 (Box 05, Folder 0178)
    Folder notes: CAE? ACR? XEN, Other markings: RS SE 830CER06
    34023001503772
  - Chapinophis, undated (Box 05, Folder 0179)
    Folder notes: CAE? Xenodermatid?, Other markings:
  - Collorhabdium, undated (Box 05, Folder 0180)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR XEN Malaya, Other markings: RS SE CO 932COL10
    34023001503749
  - Cyclocorus, 19651971 (Box 05, Folder 0181)
    Folder notes: CAE? ACR? XEN; OP, Other markings: RS SE
    34023001503731
  - Ditypophis, undated (Box 05, Folder 0182)
    Folder notes: CAE? ACR? XEN; ECS, Other markings: RS SE 881DIT07
    34023001503723
  - Dryocalamus, undated (Box 05, Folder 0183)
    Folder notes: CAE, ? ACR, ? XEN OMP, Other markings: RS SE
    34023001503715
  - Elapoidis, undated (Box 05, Folder 0184)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR XEN OM (Java, Sumatra), Other markings: RS SE 827ELA06
    34023001503681
  - Etheridgeum, undated (Box 05, Folder 0185)
    Folder notes: Wallach 1988:69 LAM-CAL?, Other markings:
    34023001503707
  - Fimbrios, undated (Box 05, Folder 0186)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR XEN -O, Other markings: RS SE CO 920FIM05
    34023001503699
  - Gonionotophis, undated (Box 05, Folder 0187)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR XEN, Other markings: SE
    34023001503673
  - Hologerrhum, undated (Box 06, Folder 0188)
    Folder notes: ACRO-DERM?, Other markings:
    34023001503665
  - Hydrablabes, undated (Box 06, Folder 0189)
    Folder notes: RS SE CAE ACR XEN? OM (Borneo)
    34023001503657
  - Lepturophis, undated (Box 06, Folder 0190)
    Folder notes: SE CAE ACR XEN, Other markings: OM (Borneo)
    34023001503921
  - Lycodon, 1971 (Box 06, Folder 0191)
    Folder notes: RS SE CO 826LYC04
    34023001503913
  - Macrocalamus, undated (Box 06, Folder 0192)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR-XEN O. Malaya, Other markings: RS SE CO 864MAC09
    34023001503905
  - Mehelya, undated (Box 06, Folder 0193)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR XEN E, Other markings: 903MEH04
    34023001503897
  - Myersophis, 1963 (Box 06, Folder 0194)
    Folder notes: CAE ?ACR, ?XEN OP, Other markings: RS SE
    34023001503863
  - Nothopsis, 19561957 (Box 06, Folder 0195)
    Folder notes: CAE ?ACR ?XEN TC-TS [MS], Other markings:
    34023001503871
  - Oreocalamus, undated (Box 06, Folder 0196)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR XEN Borneo, Other markings: RS SE CO 899ORE08
    34023001503889
  - Oxyrhabdium, 1962 (Box 06, Folder 0197)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR XEN OP, Other markings: RS SE CO
    34023001503798
  - Plagiopholis, undated (Box 06, Folder 0198)
    Folder notes: CAE XENOD ? CAE ACR? XEN? O (China), Other markings: RS
    34023001503806
  - Psammodynastes, 1972 (Box 06, Folder 0199)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM? Orient; Sulcus Centripetal, Other markings: RS SE CO 858PSA11
    34023001503814
  - Pseudapsis, 1972 (Box 06, Folder 0200)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR XEN; Hemip long spiny deeply bilopt sulcut bifurcolis centrifugal no heppatopyrre (but very distinct slibicentral ridge)., Other markings: RS SE
    34023001503822
  - Pseudorabdion, undated (Box 06, Folder 0201)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR XEN OM, Other markings: RS SE CO 862PSE10
    34023001503830
  - Pseudoxenodon, 1971 (Box 06, Folder 0202)
    Folder notes: CAE? ACR XEN-yes! OI PC, Other markings: RS SE
    34023001503848
  - Pythonodipsas, undated (Box 06, Folder 0203)
    Folder notes: CAE? ACR? XEN (ET), Other markings: SE
    34023001503855
  - Rabdion, undated (Box 06, Folder 0204)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR XEN, Other markings: RS SE CO 853RAB04
    34023001504069
  - Rhabdops, undated (Box 06, Folder 0205)
    Folder notes: CAE? ACR? XEN OI OC, Other markings: RS SE
    34023001504051
  - Scopelophis Xenodermatipae? (Natricidae?), 1990 (Box 06, Folder 0206)
    34023001504044
  - Stegonotus, undated (Box 06, Folder 0207)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR XEN OP-A (Philippines to Australia), Other markings: RS SE
    34023001504036
  - Stoliczkia, undated (Box 06, Folder 0208)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR XEN -OM, Other markings: RS SE CO 870STO07
    34023001504028
  - Tetralepsis, undated (Box 06, Folder 0209)
    Folder notes: CAE? ACR? XEN OM, Other markings: RS SE 892TET07
    34023001504010
  - Toxicocalamus "Elapidae" ?= Xenopermatidae, 1969 (Box 06, Folder 0210)
    34023001504002
  - Trachischium, undated (Box 06, Folder 0211)
    Folder notes: CAE - XENOD? CAE ACR XEN O, Other markings: RS SE
    34023001503996
  - Xenophidion (MS), 1995 (Box 06, Folder 0212)
    34023001503988
  - Xenophidion, 2004 (Box 06, Folder 0213)
    34023001503962
  - [No title], 2000 (Box 06, Folder 0214)
    Folder notes: Photographs of vertebra, Other markings: Stoliczkia; Fimbrios; Xenodermus; Achalinus; Xenophidion
    34023001503954
  - Xenophidion, undated (Box 06, Folder 0215)
    34023001503970
  - Xylophis, undated (Box 06, Folder 0216)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR XEN - 0, Other markings: RS SE CO 878XYL05
    34023001503947
  - Dipsadoboa, 1971 (Box 06, Folder 0217)
    34023001503939
  - Serpentes Colubridae: Dipsadina, undated (Box 06, Folder 0218)
    Folder notes: RS
    34023001504200
  - Atractus, 19601971 (Box 06, Folder 0219)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP ??? ???; TC-TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 828ATR05
    34023001504192
  - Coniophanes, 19691979 (Box 06, Folder 0220)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP DIP DIP NU-TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 860CON08
    34023001504184
  - Cryophis, undated (Box 06, Folder 0221)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP DIP TM; Hemipenis = Dispsadip, Other markings: RS SE CO 963CRY05
    34023001504176
  - Dipsas, 1971 (Box 06, Folder 0222)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP DIP DIP TM-TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 768DIP03
    34023001504168
  - Echinanthera, undated (Box 06, Folder 0223)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP (DIP??) See under Xenodontidae, Other markings:
    34023001504150
  - Eridiphas, undated (Box 06, Folder 0224)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP DIP LEP TM, Other markings: RS SE CO 960ERI06
    34023001504143
  - Geatractus, undated (Box 06, Folder 0225)
    34023001504077
  - Geophis, undated (Box 06, Folder 0226)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP DIP DIP TM-TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 830GEO04
    34023001504085
  - Hydromorphis, undated (Box 06, Folder 0227)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP DIP NOT? -TC, Other markings: RS SE CO 859HYD09
    34023001504093
  - Hypsiglena, 1971 (Box 06, Folder 0228)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP DIP LEP TM-NU, Other markings: RS SE CO 860HYP07
    34023001504101
  - Imantodes, 1971 (Box 06, Folder 0229)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP DIP LEP TM-TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 853IMA06
    34023001504119
  - Leptodeira, 1971 (Box 06, Folder 0230)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP DIP LEP TM-TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 843LEP07
    34023001504127
  - Ninia, 1971 (Box 06, Folder 0231)
    Folder notes: RS SE CO 853NIN02
    34023001504135
  - Pliosercus, 1971 (Box 06, Folder 0232)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP DIP DIP TM-TS; UROTHECA (PART), Other markings: RS SE CO 860PLI07
    34023001501198
  - Pseudoleptodeira, undated (Box 07, Folder 0233)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP DIP LEP TM, Other markings:
    34023001501180
  - Pseudoleptodeira, undated (Box 07, Folder 0234)
    34023001501172
  - Rhadinaea, undated (Box 07, Folder 0235)
    Folder notes: 1 of 2; CAE DIP DIP DIP NU-TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 863RHA06
    34023001501164
  - Rhadinaea, undated (Box 07, Folder 0236)
    Folder notes: 2 of 2; CAE DIP DIP DIP NU-TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 863RHA06
    34023001501156
  - Rhadinophanes, 1981 (Box 07, Folder 0237)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP DIP ??? TC, Other markings:
    34023001501149
  - Sibon, 19091971 (Box 07, Folder 0238)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP DIP DIP TM-TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 826SIB02
    34023001501404
  - Sibynomorphus, 1971 (Box 07, Folder 0239)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP DIP DIP -TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 843SIB10
    34023001501396
  - Tantalophis, 1971 (Box 07, Folder 0240)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP DIP ??? TM, Other markings: RS SE CO 958TAN08
    34023001501388
  - Tretanorhinus, undated (Box 07, Folder 0241)
    Folder notes: 1 of 2;, Other markings: RS SE CO 854TRE10
    34023001501370
  - Tretanorhinus, undated (Box 07, Folder 0242)
    Folder notes: 2 of 2;, Other markings: RS SE CO 854TRE10
    34023001501362
  - Tretanorhinus, 19391991 (Box 07, Folder 0243)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP DIP NOT; TM-TS-TW, Other markings:
    34023001501354
  - Trimetopon, undated (Box 07, Folder 0244)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP DIP?, Other markings: RE SE CO 885TRI07
    34023001501131
  - Tropidodipsas, undated (Box 07, Folder 0245)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP DIP DIP TM, Other markings: RS SE CO 858TRO10
    34023001501347
  - Urotheca, 1989 (Box 07, Folder 0246)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP DIP DIP; TM-TS, Other markings:
    34023001501271
  - Carphophis, 19481970 (Box 07, Folder 0247)
    34023001501289
  - Contia, undated (Box 07, Folder 0248)
    Folder notes: (Temp)
    34023001501305
  - Diadophis, 1970 (Box 07, Folder 0249)
    34023001501297
  - Farancia, 1971 (Box 07, Folder 0250)
    34023001501313
  - Heterodon, undated (Box 07, Folder 0251)
    34023001501321
  - Xenodontines, undated (Box 07, Folder 0252)
    34023001501339
  - Pseudoboini, undated (Box 07, Folder 0253)
    34023001516899
  - Alsophis, 1968 (Box 07, Folder 0254)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN ALS TW, Other markings: RS SE CO 862ALS05
    34023001516907
  - Antillophis, undated (Box 07, Folder 0255)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN ALS TW, Other markings:
    34023001516915
  - Arrhython, 1969 (Box 07, Folder 0256)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN ALS TW, Other markings: RS SE CO 858ARR05
    34023001516923
  - Calamodontophis, undated (Box 07, Folder 0257)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN TAC TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 963CAL12
    34023001516931
  - Clelia, 1968 (Box 07, Folder 0258)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN SEY TS_TM, Other markings: RS SE CO 826CLE03
    34023001516949
  - Conophis, 19681971 (Box 07, Folder 0259)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN ??? TC-TM, Other markings: RS SE CO 860CON05
    34023001516873
  - Darlingtonia, 1971 (Box 07, Folder 0260)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN ALS TW, Other markings: RS SE CO 935DAR09
    34023001516881
  - Ditaxodon, undated (Box 07, Folder 0261)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN PHI? TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 958DIT06
    34023001516865
  - Drepanoides, undated (Box 07, Folder 0262)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP YEN SCY TS, Other markings:
    34023001516964
  - Dromicus =Alsophis, undated (Box 07, Folder x)
  - Echinanthera, undated (Box 07, Folder 0263)
    Folder notes: DIP XEN?, Other markings:
    34023001516972
  - Elapomorphus, undated (Box 07, Folder 0264)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN PHI? TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 853ELA09
    34023001516998
  - Enuliophis, undated (Box 07, Folder 0265)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN - TM-TS, Other markings:
    34023001516980
  - Enulius, 1968 (Box 07, Folder 0266)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN ??? TS-TM, Other markings: RS SE CO 871ENU04
    34023001517004
  - Erythrolamprus, undated (Box 07, Folder 0267)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN XEN TS-TC, Other markings: RS SE CO 830ERY11
    34023001517012
  - Gomesophis, undated (Box 07, Folder 0268)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN TAC TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 959GOM07
    34023001517020
  - Helicops, 1971 (Box 07, Folder 0269)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN ALS, Other markings: RS SE CO 830HEL05
    34023001517038
  - Hydrodynastes, 1970 (Box 08, Folder 0270)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN ALS TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 843HYD10
    34023001517061
  - Hydrops, 1969 (Box 08, Folder 0271)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN ??? TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 830HYD04
    34023001517079
  - Hypsirhynchus, 1971 (Box 08, Folder 0272)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN ALS TW, Other markings: RS SE CO 858HYP10
    34023001517087
  - Ialtris, 1972 (Box 08, Folder 0273)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN ALS? TN, Other markings: RS SE CO 862IAL04
    34023001517053
  - Lioheterophis, 1969 (Box 08, Folder 0274)
    Folder notes: CAE XEN ??? ???, Other markings: RS SE CO 943LIO10
    34023001517046
  - Liophis, 1969 (Box 08, Folder 0275)
    Folder notes: 1 of 2; CAE DIP XEN XEN TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 830LIO04
    34023001516840
  - Liophis, 1969 (Box 08, Folder 0276)
    34023001516857
  - Lystrophis, 1968 (Box 08, Folder 0277)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN SEN TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 885LYS07
    34023001516832
  - Marcroprotodon, undated (Box 08, Folder 0278)
    Folder notes: [Boiginae], Other markings: RS SE CO 850MAC10
    34023001516816
  - Manolepis, 1971 (Box 08, Folder 0279)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN PHI? TM, Other markings: RS SE CO 885MAN06
    34023001516824
  - Oxyrhopus, 1971 (Box 08, Folder 0280)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN SCY TS-TM, Other markings: RS SE CO 830OXY06
    34023001516956
  - Philodryas, 1968 (Box 08, Folder 0281)
    Folder notes: 1 of 2: CAE DIP XEN PHI TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 830PHI07
    34023001517178
  - Philodryas, 1968 (Box 08, Folder 0282)
    Folder notes: 2 of 2;, Other markings:
    34023001517186
  - Phimophis, 1971 (Box 08, Folder 0283)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN SCY TS-TC, Other markings: RS SE CO 860PHI06
    34023001517228
  - Platyinion, undated (Box 08, Folder 0284)
    Folder notes: Philopryas (Thobias+), Other markings: RS SE CO 923PLA07
    34023001517210
  - Pseudablabes, 1971 (Box 08, Folder 0285)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN TAC TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 896PSE09
    34023001517202
  - Pseudoboa, 1971 (Box 08, Folder 0286)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN SEV, Other markings: RS SE CO 801PSE06
    34023001517194
  - Pseudoeryx, 1968 (Box 08, Folder 0287)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN ??? TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 826PSE07
    34023001517160
  - Pseudotomodon, undated (Box 08, Folder 0288)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN TAC TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 896PSE10
    34023001517152
  - Psomophis, undated (Box 08, Folder 0289)
    Folder notes: CAE XEN PSE TS, Other markings:
    34023001517145
  - Ptychophis, 1971 (Box 08, Folder 0290)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN TAC TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 915PTY07
    34023001517137
  - Rhachidelus, undated (Box 08, Folder 0291)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN SCY TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 908RAC07
    34023001517129
  - Sphenophis, undated (Box 08, Folder 0292)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN ??? TS, Other markings: RS SE CO
    34023001517111
  - Siphlophis, 1971 (Box 08, Folder 0293)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN SCY TS-TC, Other markings: RS SE CO 846SIP07
    34023001517103
  - Sordellina, undated (Box 08, Folder 0294)
    Folder notes: CAE DEP XEN ??? TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 923SOR07
    34023001517095
  - Tachymenis, 1971 (Box 08, Folder 0295)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN TAC TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 835TAC07
    34023001517368
  - Taeniophallus, undated (Box 08, Folder 0296)
    Folder notes: CAE XEN ? PSE, Other markings:
    34023001517350
  - Thamnodynastes, undated (Box 08, Folder 0297)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN TAC TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 830THA11
    34023001517327
  - Tomodon, undated (Box 08, Folder 0298)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN TAC TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 853TOM04
    34023001517335
  - Trypanurgos, 1971 (Box 08, Folder 0299)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEP SCY TS-TC, Other markings: RS SE CO 843TRI08
    34023001517343
  - Tropidodipsas Leucomelas= Tripanurgos, undated (Box 08, Folder 0300)
    34023001517319
  - Tropidodryas, undated (Box 08, Folder 0301)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP KEN PHI TS, Other markings:
    34023001517475
  - Umbrivaga, undated (Box 08, Folder 0302)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN XEN TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 964UMB06
    34023001517467
  - Uromacer, 1972 (Box 08, Folder 0303)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN ALS TW, Other markings: RS SE CO 853URO05
    34023001517509
  - Uromacerina, 1972 (Box 08, Folder 0304)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN ALS? TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 930URO08
    34023001517244
  - Waglerophis, undated (Box 08, Folder 0305)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN XEN TS, Other markings: RS SE CO
    34023001517301
  - Xenodon, 1968 (Box 08, Folder 0306)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN XEN TS-TM, Other markings: RS SE CO 827XEN04
    34023001517293
  - Caenophidia, undated (Box 08, Folder 0307)
    34023001517491
  - Amastridium, 1969 (Box 08, Folder 0308)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP? DIP? TM-TC, Other markings: RS SE CO 861AMA08
    34023001517483
  - Ancient addresses, undated (Box 08, Folder 0309)
    34023001517459
  - Nothopsis, 1972 (Box 08, Folder 0310)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR XEN TC-TS XEN?, Other markings: RS SE CO 871NOT06
    34023001517442
  - Crisantophis, 1970 (Box 08, Folder 0311)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP DIP ??? TC Possible Xenodermatid, Other markings: RS SE CO
    34023001517434
  - Adelphicos, 1972 (Box 08, Folder 0312)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR XENOD? TM-TC, Other markings: RS SE CO 862ADE07
    34023001517426
  - Apostolepis, 1972 (Box 08, Folder 0313)
    Folder notes: CAE DIP XEN TAC TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 861APO08
    34023001517418
  - Chersodromus, 1972 (Box 08, Folder 0314)
    Folder notes: CAE TM XEN DER Xenodermatid, Other markings: RS SE CO 860CHE09
    34023001517376
  - Xenopholis, 1972 (Box 08, Folder 0315)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR XEN XED TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 869XEN07
    34023001517384
  - Synophis, 1972 (Box 08, Folder 0316)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR XEN TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 896SYN05
    34023001517392
  - Emmochliophis, 1972 (Box 08, Folder 0317)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR XEN NOT TS (per synophis?) ?? ACHALINOS/FIMBRIOS?, Other markings:
    34023001517400
  - Diaphorolepis, 1971 (Box 08, Folder 0318)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR XEN TC-TS, Other markings: RS SE CO 863DIA10
    34023001514845
  - Rhynchocalamus, 1972 (Box 08, Folder 0319)
    34023001514837
  - Lytorhynchus, 1972 (Box 09, Folder 0320)
    Folder notes: RS SE CO 863LYT09
    34023001514829
  - Unknown, undated (Box 09, Folder 0321)
    34023001514811
  - Cercophis, undated (Box 09, Folder 0322)
    34023001514803
  - Rhynchophis, undated (Box 09, Folder 0323)
    Folder notes: CAEN Oligodontidae??, Other markings: RS SE CO 897RHY08
    34023001514795
  - Treniophallus, undated (Box 09, Folder 0324)
    34023001514787
  - Thermophis, undated (Box 09, Folder 0325)
    Folder notes: CAE PACR ? XEN PC Tibet, Other markings: RS SE CO 953THE07
    34023001514779
  - Acrochordidae, 1969 (Box 09, Folder 0326)
    Folder notes: ICA SEC FAC, Other markings: HP
    34023001514761
  - Acrochordus, 1977 (Box 09, Folder 0327)
    Folder notes: Dowling MS 1977!, Other markings:
    34023001514753
  - Bitia, undated (Box 09, Folder 0328)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR HOM - O, Other markings: RS SE CO 842BIT02
    34023001514712
  - Cantoria, undated (Box 09, Folder 0329)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR HOM - O, Other markings: RS SE CO 857CAN05
    34023001514746
  - Cerberus, undated (Box 09, Folder 0330)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR HOM - O, Other markings: RS SE CO 829CER05
    34023001514738
  - Enhydris, 1971 (Box 09, Folder 0331)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR HOM - O, Other markings: RS SE CO 802ENH05
    34023001514720
  - Erpeton, 1972 (Box 09, Folder 0332)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR HOM - O, Other markings: RS SE CO 800ERP04
    34023001514936
  - Fordonia, 1971 (Box 09, Folder 0333)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR HOM - O, Other markings: RS SE CO 842FOR05
    34023001514985
  - Gerarda, undated (Box 09, Folder 0334)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR HOM - O, Other markings: RS SE CO 849GER04
    34023001514977
  - Heurnia, undated (Box 09, Folder 0335)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR HOM - A, Other markings: RS SE CO 926HEU04
    34023001514969
  - Homalopsis, undated (Box 09, Folder 0336)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR HOM - O, Other markings: RS SE CO 822HOM07
    34023001514951
  - Myron, 1971 (Box 09, Folder 0337)
    Folder notes: CAE ACR HOM - A, Other markings: RS SE CO 849MYR02
    34023001514944
  - CAE LAM LAN Langahinae, undated (Box 09, Folder 0338)
    34023001514928
  - Allluaudina, undated (Box 09, Folder 0339)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM LAN LAN IM, Other markings: MAD
    34023001514902
  - Geodipsas, 1970 (Box 09, Folder 0340)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM LAN LAN E, IM, Other markings: RS SE CO 896GEO06
    34023001514910
  - Ithycyphus, undated (Box 09, Folder 0341)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM LAN LAN MAD, Other markings: RS SE CO 873ITH07
    34023001514886
  - Langaha, undated (Box 09, Folder 0342)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM LAN LAN MAD, Other markings: RS SE CO 784LAN04
    34023001514860
  - Lycodryas, undated (Box 09, Folder 0343)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM LAN LAN MAD, Other markings: RS SE CO 879LYC06
  - Madagascarophis, 1971 (Box 09, Folder 0344)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM LAN LAN MAD, Other markings: RS SE CO 952MAD12
    34023001514878
  - Montaspis [=Geodipsas], undated (Box 09, Folder 0345)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM LAN LAN MAD, Other markings:
    34023001514852
  - Pythonodipsas, undated (Box 09, Folder 0346)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM LAN LAN, Other markings: RS SE CO 868PYT10
    34023001515065
  - Stenophis, undated (Box 09, Folder 0347)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM LAN LAN, Other markings: Removed from ? of Lycophras? (Resin/2 Comorus) Malaghey? Memrus? only
    34023001515073
  - Brygophis, undated (Box 09, Folder 0348)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM LAN ?? PSE?, Other markings:
    34023001515081
  - Compsophis, undated (Box 09, Folder 0349)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM LAN PSE [??] MAD, Other markings: RS SE CO 894COM07
    34023001515107
  - Pseudoxyrhophinae, undated (Box 09, Folder 0350)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM LAN LAN MAD, Other markings: RS SE CO 894COM07
  - Dromicodryas, 1971 (Box 09, Folder 0350)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM LAN PSE 1M, Other markings: 893DRO09
    34023001515099
  - Heteroliodon, undated (Box 09, Folder 0351)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM LAN PSE 1M, Other markings: RS SE CO 913HET09
    34023001515123
  - Leioheterodon, 1968 (Box 09, Folder 0352)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM LAN PSE MAD, Other markings: RS SE CO 893 LIO09
    34023001515115
  - Liopholidophis, 1971 (Box 09, Folder 0353)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM LAM PSE MAD, Other markings: RS SE CO 904LIO11
    34023001515032
  - Liophidium, undated (Box 09, Folder 0354)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM LAN PSE MAD, Other markings: RS SE CO 896LIO07
    34023001515040
  - Micropisthodon, undated (Box 09, Folder 0355)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM LAN PSE, Other markings:
    34023001515057
  - Pararhadinea, undated (Box 09, Folder 0356)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM LAN PSE MAD, Other markings: RS SE CO 898PAR09
    34023001515024
  - Pseudoxyrhopus, undated (Box 09, Folder 0357)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM LAN PSE MAD, Other markings: RS SE CO 881PSE11
    34023001517285
  - African Colubrids, undated (Box 09, Folder 0358)
    34023001517277
  - Lamprophis, 1970 (Box 09, Folder 0359)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM LAM LAM E, Other markings: 843LAM07, see also Boaedon
    34023001517269
  - Oligodon Figures, undated (Box 09, Folder 0360)
    34023001517251
  - Oligodon Jan, undated (Box 09, Folder 0361)
    34023001517236
  - Oligodon: Wall 1923, undated (Box 09, Folder 0362)
    34023001514993
  - Oligodon: Taxonomy, undated (Box 09, Folder 0363)
    34023001515016
  - Oligodon: Geography, undated (Box 09, Folder 0364)
  - Oligodon, 1972 (Box 09, Folder 0365)
    34023001515214
  - Lycodonomorphus, 1972 (Box 09, Folder 0366)
    Folder notes: CAE E, Other markings: 843LYC12
    34023001515230
  - Pseudoboodon, undated (Box 09, Folder 0367)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM LAM LAM, Other markings: 897PSE09
    34023001515222
  - Chamaelycus, undated (Box 09, Folder 0368)
    Folder notes: CAE LAM LAM LYC, Other markings: 919CHA08
    34023001515248